（嘶嘶声）
(whooshing sound)
（贴纸弹出）
(sticker popping)
（嘶嘶声）
(whooshing sound)
- 数据集加上数据帧等于真爱。
- Datasets and DataFrames equals love.
虽然 Datasets 库的处理函数
Although the processing functions of the Datasets library
将涵盖训练模型所需的大部分情况，
will cover most of the cases needed to train a model,
有时你需要切换到其它库
there are times when you'll need to switch to a library
比如 Pandas 来获得更强大的功能
like Pandas to access more powerful features
或针对计算机视觉使用更高级的 API。
or high level APIs for visualization.
幸运的是，Datasets 库是专门为了
Fortunately, the Datasets library is designed
和外部库进行互操作所设计的，比如 Pandas
to be interoperable with libraries like Pandas,
此外还有 NumPy、PyTorch、TensorFlow 和 JAX。
as well as NumPy, PyTorch, TensorFlow and JAX.
在本视频中，我们将了解
In this video, we'll take a look
我们如何将数据格式快速切换到 Pandas DataFrames
at how we can quickly switch our data
并且再切换回来。
to Pandas DataFrames and back.
例如，假设我们正在分析
As an example, let's suppose we're analyzing
来自瑞士的最高法院案件。
Supreme Court cases from Switzerland.
像往常一样，我们使用 load_dataset 函数
As usual, we download our dataset from the hub
从 hub 下载我们的数据集。
using the load_dataset function.
你可以看到训练集的第一个元素
And you can see that the first element of the training set
是一个普通的 Python 字典类型
is an ordinary Python dictionary
里面包含各种我们需要的字段。
with various fields of interest.
现在，假设在我们训练任何模型之前，
Now, suppose that before we train any models,
我们想稍微浏览一下数据。
we'd like to explore the data a bit.
例如，我们可能希望知道
For example, we might be interested in knowing
哪些法律领域最常见
which legal areas are the most common
或者我们可能想知道语言
or we might wanna know how the languages
在各个地区是如何分布的。
are distributed across regions.
使用原生 Arrow 类型
Answering these questions
很难回答这些问题，
with the native Arrow format isn't easy,
但我们可以快速切换到 Pandas 来获得答案。
but we can quickly switch to Pandas to get our answers.
通过使用 set_format 方法即可实现，
The way this works is that by using the set_format method,
我们将更改数据集的输出格式
we will change the output format of the dataset
从 Python 字典类型到 Pandas DataFrame 类型。
from Python dictionaries to Pandas DataFrames.
正如你在此示例中所见，
As you can see in this example,
数据集中的每一行都表示为一个 DataFrame，
each row in the dataset is represented as a DataFrame,
所以我们可以对整个数据集进行切片
so we can slice the whole dataset
来获取语料库的单个 DataFrame。
to get a single DataFrame of the corpus.
其底层工作原理
The way this works under the hood,
是 datasets 库改变了
is that the datasets library changes
数据集中神奇的 __getitem__ 方法。
the magic __getitem__ method of the dataset.
对于 Python 容器来说 __getitem__ 方法
The __getitem__ method is a special method
是一种特殊的方法，它允许你指定
for Python containers that allows you
以何种方式使用索引。
to specify how indexing works.
在这种情况下，原始数据集的 __getitem__ 方法
In this case, the __getitem__ method of the raw dataset
首先返回一个 Python 字典
starts off by returning a Python dictionary
然后在调用 set_format 之后，
and then after applying set_format,
我们更改 __getitem__ 以返回 DataFrames。
we change __getitem__ to return DataFrames instead.
如果你想做格式转换
The Datasets library also provides a to_pandas method
并一次性对数据集进行切片
if you wanna do the format conversion
Datasets 库还提供了一个 to_pandas 方法。
and slicing of the dataset in one go.
一旦你有了一个 DataFrame，
And once you have a DataFrame,
你可以找到各种复杂问题的答案
you can find the answers to all sorts of complex questions
或使用你最喜欢的可视化库绘制图表。
or make plots with your favorite visualization library.
唯一要记住的
The only thing to remember
是一旦你完成了 Pandas 分析，
is that once you're done with your Pandas analysis,
你应该将输出格式重置回 Arrow 表。
you should reset the output format back to Arrow tables.
如果不这样做，当你尝试词元化你的文本
If you don't, you can run into problems
可能会遇到问题
if you try to tokenize your text
因为它不再是字典中的
because it is no longer represented
字符串。
as strings in a dictionary.
通过重置输出格式，我们得到 Arrow 表
By resetting the output format we get back Arrow tables
我们可以毫无顾虑地进行词元化。
and we can tokenize without problem.
（嘶嘶声）
(whooshing sound)